Resume 18/10/23, 2:08 PM

# **BHARAT JETHMALANI**

**STUDENT** 

### **SUMMARY**

Detail oriented, accurate and analytical student with strong grasp in computational techniques, algorithms and logic . Armed with these skills and experience in startup companies, my aim is to contribute towards building amore analytical approach to solve business and economical problems. Complete team player with excellent communication skills with a proven talent for learning quickly in a result orientated environment.

### **EDUCATION**

Conestoga College Post Graduation Diploma Business Analytics 2024	Sept. 2023 - Current
Conestoga College Post Graduation Diploma Predictive Analytics 2023	Jan. 2023 - Aug. 2023
School Of Mathematical Sciences, NMIMS Bsc. Mathematics(Hons) 2022 CGPA - 3.07/4	July 2019 - Apr. 2022
Shree Bhavan's Bharti Public School, Bhopal XII Science 2019 74%	Apr. 2018 - Mar. 2019
Shree Bhavan's Bharti Public School, Bhopal X 2017	Apr. 2016 - Mar. 2017

#### **EMPLOYMENT**

Factory Shoe, Customer Service Representative, Kitchener	Mar. 2023 - Current
Warehouse Manager, Manjeet Industries, Bhopal Worked in warehouse of machinery and have managed inventory on daily basis	May 2022 - Nov. 2022
Pappytech Solution Private Limited, Customer Service Representative, Mumbai	Dec. 2021 - Apr. 2022
Pappytech Solution Private Limited, E-commerce Executive, Mumbai	Apr. 2022 - Nov. 2022
Bazarville, E-Commerce Intern, Bhopal Bazarville is an apparel company which makes customised t-shirts and sell of different platforms	Aug. 2021 - Oct. 2021
Bazarville, Data Analytics Intern, Bhopal Bazarville is an apparel company which makes customised t-shirts	Jan. 2021 - July 2021

### **SKILLS**

TECHNICAL SKILLS: Python, MATLAB, Mircrosoft Office, Spyder, R Language
INTERPERSONAL SKILLS: Communication, Exceptional Leadership Skills, Good Work Ethics, Good Problem Solver, Data Entry, Customer Service
LANGUAGES: English, Hindi

## **PROJECTS**

Stock Prediction using Python and Spyder	July 2021 - May 2022

### **AWARDS**

National Level Chess Player, FIDE India Represented Madhya Pradesh State in a National tournament	Sept. 2017
State Level Badminton Player, Madhya Pradesh State Represented Bhopal city in a State tournament	June 2015
State Level Table Tennis Player, Madhya Pradesh State Represented Bhopal city in a State tournament	May 2015
Divisional Level Cricket Player, Bhopal	Jan. 2014

### **VOLUNTEERING**

Rotaract Club Of Bombay Juhu Beach, Director of Membership Team	July 2020 - June 2021
Mumbai	

Part of a well known club of Mumbai

### **AVAILAILITY**

https://resume.creddle.io/